When you’re on the lam, they call the ham.
Hitpig! is a animation, comedy, adventure film directed by David Feiss.
A porcine bounty hunter accepts his next hit:
Pickles, a naive, ebullient elephant.
Though he initially sets out to capture the perky pachyderm, the unlikely pair find themselves
crisscrossing the globe on an adventure that brings out the best in both of them.
Hitpig (voice), played by Jason Sudeikis.
Pickles (voice), played by Lilly Singh.
Leapin' Lord of the Leotard (voice), played by Rainn Wilson.
Leticia dos Anjos (voice), played by Anitta.
Koala (voice), played by Hannah Gadsby.
Polecat (voice), played by RuPaul.
is a 2024 animated comedy film directed by Cinzia Angelini and David Feiss.
The film comes from an original story by Berkeley Breathed,
rooted from his 2008 children's book Pete & Pickles.
Breathed also wrote the screenplay alongside Dave Rosenbaum and Tyler Werrin.
Produced by Aniventure and animated by Cinesite, the film features the voices of Jason
Sudeikis, Lilly Singh, Rainn Wilson, Anitta, RuPaul, Hannah Gadsby and Charlie Adler.
was released in North America on 1 November 2024.
The film explores themes of friendship, bounty hunter,
hitman, animal species, futuristic.
The tone is lighthearted.